Kravchenko Liudmyla Name:

Home address: Solom'yans'kyi district, Kyiv, Ukraine

Mobile number: +38 (050) 331-21-50 E-Mail: luisiya@gmail.com



Summary of qualifications:

I have been working as frontend-end developer freelancer for more than one year. I've gained experience in building web application and services for commercial project of CRM

I have successfully applied my skills in Javascript, HTML5, Sass, WebPack. In order to advance my skills and knowledge, I have recently started studying React Fundamentals.

In addition, I have general skills in graphics editors, such as Photoshop and 3DStudio MAX. On previous positions I had an experience in design, development and administration of the database for the construction of BS network. I've successfully completed Harvard CS50 programming courses (BrainBasket Foundation).

Skills:

- JavaScript(ES5, ES6)
- HTML
- CSS/Sass
- Bootsrap
- Materialize

- Gulp
- - Webpack
- C++ basics

GIT

Python basics

Work experience:

Freelance in Frontend-end development for commercial project of CRM System March 2017 – now

Agile business development and SCRUM

- Development of CRM System as an important part of a Scrum team.
- Implemented filters and sorting functionalities using JS in accordance with customer requirements.
- Render of the data using JS classes for dynamic generation of HTML table;
- Inline CRUD of table entries;
- Gulp/Webpack used;
- Facilitation of a team in a Scrum master role (part-time).
- Applying SCRUM ceremonies.
- The link to the demo version of the project: https://luisiya.github.io/crm_update/CRM_update/dist/html/

VF Ukraine (former Vodafone Ukraine), Kyiv, Ukraine January 2010 - February 2017

Engineer of the 2nd category, Technical Directorate, Infrastructure Access Network Implementation Group

- Administration of the database for the construction of BS network;
- Participation in the modernization and improvement of the functionality of E-WorkOrder electronic system (preparation of requirement specification);
- Ensuring the implementation of the plan for the construction of base stations in the Central Region of Ukraine (control and management of timely project execution);
- Controlling of interaction processes between Territorial Offices and Contractors;

MTS Ukraine (former UMC), Kyiv, Ukraine

January 2010 – July 2005

Engineer, Project Management Department, BSS Development Department

- Coordination of GSM Network Expansion Project implementation with General Contractor;
- Control of implementation responsibilities by General Contractor according to the Turnkey Agreement;
- Project Management: Creation of centralized system of data handling, exchanging and saving all information and documentation concerning processes of building BS.

Golden Telecom, Account Manager July 2005 – September 2004

- Sales of services and subscriber equipment of fixed communication (telephony, data transfer, Internet);
- Holding negotiations with potential/existing clients, giving consultations on all the company's services.

Education:

• 2003-2004

State University of Information and Communication Technologies, **Master of Science Degree in Telecommunications with distinction**.

The main specialization is Technology of Switch Centers.

• 2000-2002

London school of English, Kiev, Ukraine.

Upper-intermediate course.

• 1999 - 2000

Bachelor of Science Degree in Telecommunications, State University of Information and Communications Technologies (Information Networks faculty); obtained a distinction.

Trainings / practice:

| 2018 REACT, GoIT | 2018 Java Script, GolT |
|---|--|
| 2017 HTML, CSS, SASS, Gulp GoIT | 2017 Basic Algorithm Scripting, CodeAcademy |
| 2017 CS50: Introduction to Computer Science | 2017 Beginner's course of German, Language school |
| 2016 Basic JavaScript, CodeAcademy | 2016 Basic Front End Development Project, CodeAcademy |
| 2016 jQuery, CodeAcademy | 2016 HTML&CSS, CodeAcademy |
| 2016 Business English, Prometheus school | 2016 SQL Fundamentals, Codecademy |
| 2015 Upper-Intermediate course of English | 2012 SAP CFM, MTS, Kyiv |
| 2007 Interface Russia, Planning, installation, configuration and administration Microsoft Office Project Server 2003 | 2007 Interface Russia, Special aspects of Project Management with MS Project |
| 2006 Kvazar-Micro Education Center, Microsoft Access 2003 | 2005 IBM Russia, Project Management Fundamentals |
| 2005 AcadEx, U14404 - IBM Lotus Notes 6 Course | 2005 NAU Consulting Group, Technology of effective sales |
| 2005 Golden Telecom, Account Manager School | 2004 Sales Basics training, IIB |

Additional information:

| , .a.a | |
|------------------|--|
| PC skills: | MS Windows, Word, Excel, Visio, Power Point, Access, Outlook, Lotus, SAP, 3DStudio MAX, SketchUp, HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, C++ basics, Python basics, Git, Gulp, Adobe Photoshop, Sublime Text, WebStorm |
| Language skills: | Native Russian and Ukrainian, fluent English, German basics |
| Possible trips: | Biometric passport |
| Hobby: | Development, painting, running |

Personal:

| r croonar. | |
|---------------------|---|
| Date of birth: | January 20, 1981 |
| Personal abilities: | Responsibility, highly-organized, good interpersonal skills, determination, |
| | creative, easy and quick learning, energetic, punctuality. |